Guide to the Dana Tai Soon Burgess Dance Company records, 1988-2012 MS2030
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Dana Tai Soon Burgess Dance Company records
1988-2012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Burgess, Dana Tai Soon
MS2030
6.75 Linear Feet
Dana Tai Soon Burgess & Co., formerly the Moving Forward Contemporary Asian American Dance Company records consists of material dating from 1988 to 2012, which covers the emergence and rise of Dana Tai Soon Burgess and the Moving Forward Contemporary Asian American Dance Company in the Washington, DC performing arts community.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Biographical Note
Dana Tai Soon Burgess was born in Carmel, CA to artist parents Joseph and Anna. While Dana was still a young child, the Burgesses moved to Santa Fe, NM, where he was first introduced to dance at the age of 16. In 1985, Dana graduated from Santa Fe High School and moved to Albuquerque, NM, where he studied dance and Asian history at the University of New Mexico. After finishing college in 1990, Dana moved to Washington, DC and began auditioning and performing in the metropolitan area. In 1991 he founded Moving Forward Contemporary Asian American Dance Company as a way to explore issues concerning Asian American identity. Dana also began organizing a summer program for young Asian American dancers called Moving Forward Asian American Youth Dance Program. He enrolled in the George Washington University, where he earned a Masters in Fine Arts in 1994. In 2005, the company name became Dana Tai Soon Burgess & Co.
Throughout his career Dana Tai Soon Burgess has danced with distinguished artists, performed at prestigious theaters, and taught hundreds of students. He trained with Tim Wengerd, Bill Evens, and Jill Wantanabe. He has received grants from the DC Commission for the Arts and Humanities and the DC Community Humanities Council, as well as corporate sponsors such as Anheuser Busch, the Meyer Foundation, and AT&T. His work has been performed in numerous venues, including Dance Place, the Corcoran Gallery of Art, the Kennedy Center; as well as La Mama, the United Nations and the Lincoln Center Out of Doors in New York. He has taught at the Kirov Academy in DC, the Hamborg Ballet, and the Washington Ballet; as well as the George Mason University, the University of Maryland, and Georgetown University. He was awarded the Mayor's Arts Award for Outstanding Emerging Artist in 1994. He has also served on the board of the Asian American Arts Alliance and was appointed to the Commission for the Arts and Humanities for the District of Columbia.
Collection Scope and Content
The Dana Tai Soon Burgess & Co., formerly the Moving Forward Contemporary Asian American Dance Company records consists of material dating from 1988 to 2012, which covers the emergence and rise of Dana Tai Soon Burgess and the Moving Forward Contemporary Asian American Dance Company in the Washington, DC performing arts community. Included in the collection are performance files, administrative files, audiovisual material, such as photographs and videocassettes, and oversize material.
The Dana Tai Soon Burgess & Co. and Moving Forward Contemporary Asian American Dance Company Records are part of the Dance Archives of the Greater Washington Region. The Archives was established in 1993 by Nancy Diers Johnson, Ed.D., Associate Professor of Dance, and the Gelman Library of the George Washington University. The Dance Archives of the Greater Washington Region collects, preserves and makes accessible the documentary heritage of all forms and types of dance.
Collection Organization
Organized into six series: Performace files, Administrative files, Publications, Newspaper clippings, Audiovisual material, and Oversize material.
Modern dance; DVDs; Photographs; Washington (D.C.); Videocassettes; Performing arts; Dance; George Washington University--Alumni and alumnae; Moving Forward: Contemporary Asian American Dance Company; Dana Tai Soon Burgess Dance Company; Dana Tai Soon Burgess & Co.; Burgess, Dana Tai Soon
- Performance files, 1988-2008; MS2030 Series 1
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains programs, calendars, and flyers pertaining to performances.
  - Joint Actions, Experimental Theatre, University of New Mexico, 1988 April 25-27 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
  - Articulations, Experimental Theatre, University of New Mexico, 1988 April 28-30 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Convergence, University of New Mexico, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Country Tails, University of New Mexico, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Tim Wengerd and Company, Kimo Theatre, Albuquerque, NM, 1988 October 21-22 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Choreographer's Showcase, Center for Contemporary Arts, Albuquerque, NM, 1988 July 01-02 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bradley Lake, Dance Place, Washington, DC, 1989 August 19-20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dance Place, Washington, DC, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Trial of Orestes, The Shakespeare Theatre, Washington, DC, 1992 March 12-16 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - In Series, Mount Vernon College, Washington, DC, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Peace Thru Art Week, American University, Washington, DC, 1992 April 06-11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Spring Dance Concert, Marvin Center Theatre, George Washington University, Washington, DC, 1992 April 14-16 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Spring Performance, Black Movements Dance Theatre, Georgetown University, Washington, DC, 1992 April 23-26 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 64 Beds, The Jefferson Memorial, Washington, DC, 1992 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mayor's Arts Awards, Lisner Auditorium, George Washington University, Washington, DC, 1992 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dance/Performance Concert, Marvin Center Theatre, George Washington University, Washington, DC, 1992 November 19-21 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Dance Place, Washington, DC, 1992 December 12-13 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - WPA Cabaret Re-Voltaire, Main Gallery, Washington, DC, 1992 December 18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Open Stage - Rio 92, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Convocation, Lisner Auditorium, George Washington University, Washington, DC, 1993 January 26 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Monday Night at the National, The National Theatre, Washington, DC, 1993 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Body Language, Black Movements Dance Theatre, Georgetown University, Washington, DC, 1993 April 23-25 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - DC ART/WORKS, University of the District of Columbia, Washington, DC, 1993 August 03-04 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - In Series, Mount Vernon College, Washington, DC, 1993 October 15-16 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Mayor's Arts Awards, Lisner Auditorium, George Washington University, Washington, DC, 1993 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Moving Forward, Marvin Center Theatre, George Washington University, Washington, DC, 1993 December 10-11 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Searching for the Sun and Moon, Freer Gallery of Art, Washington, DC, 1994 April 15-17 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Kaleidoscope, Spring Concert, Georgetown University, Washington, DC, 1994 April 28-30 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Asian Pacific American Heritage Month, Resolution Trust Corporation, 1994 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Summer youth program performance, Kennedy Center Theatre Lab, Washington, DC, 1994 August 01 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Mayor's Art Awards, Lisner Auditorium, George Washington University, Washington, DC, 1994 October 24 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - The Second Asian Contemporary Dance Festival, La MaMa Experimental Theatre Club, New York, NY, 1994 December 01-02 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Passages from the Journey, Dance Place, Washington, DC, 1995 January 21-22 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Seung Hwa: Rape/Race/Rage/Revolution, 1995 March 16-19 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Asian American Dance Festival Part Two, University of Wisconsin, Madison, 1995 April 08 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - A Celebration of Asian-American Dance, Front and Center!, The Kennedy Center, Washington, DC, 1995 April 13 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Asian Pacific American Awareness Day, Washington, DC, 1995 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Tracing in Solitude, Staff Celebration of the 50th Anniversary of the United Nations, 1995 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Summer youth program performance, The Kennedy Center Theatre Lab, Washington, DC, 1995 August 07 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Lincoln Center Out of Doors, New York, NY, 1995 August 20 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Reston Community Center, Reston, VA, 1995 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - In Series, Mount Vernon College, Washington, DC, 1995 September 29-30 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Michio Ito revival, Dance Place, Washington, DC, 1996 January 20 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Public Humanities Award, Meridian International Center, Washington, DC, 1996 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 3rd Annual Asian Heritage Month Festival, Toronto, Canada, 1996 May (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Solos, Warner Theatre, Washington, DC, 1996 May 01-02 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Voices From Within - An Asian American Exploration, Dorothy Madden Theatre, University of Maryland, College Park, MD, 1996 May 08 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Cultures in Motion: Perspectives on Asian American Dance, Asian Pacific American Heritage Month, National Portrait Gallery, Washington, DC, 1996 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Il Muestra de Danza Universitaria, Caracas, Venezuela, 1996 June 01-02 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Experamental de Danza "Pisorrojo," Caracas, Venezuela, 1996 July 13 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - XII Festival de Jóvenes Coreógrapfos, Caracas, Venezuela, 1996 August 22-September 15 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Going Publick, Publick Playhouse, Cheverly, MD, 1996 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Asians in the Americas, Part I, Dance Place, Washington, DC, 1997 January 24-26 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Program Calendar: 1997 Spring, Dance Place (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Spring Dance Concert, George Washington University, Washington, DC, 1997 April 24-26 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 2nd Annual Asia in Washington, Asian/Pacific Islander American Heritage Month, Kennedy Center, Washington, DC, 1997 May 08 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Dance Place, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - 1997 Fall, University of Maryland, The Arts at Maryland (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Program calendar: The Kennedy Center, Performances for School Groups, Professional Development for Teachers, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - The Nightingale, Theatre Lab, Kennedy Center, Washington, DC, 1997 October 24-November 09 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Asians in the Americas, Part II, 1997 November 14-16 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Helix, 1998 February 12 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Asia in Washington: Contemporary Visions, 1998 May 07 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Outsider/Insider: Asian American Journeys, October 23; Across Bridges of Masks and Song: Dance and Music of Korea, October 24, 1998 October 23-24 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Performing Arts Center, Purchase College - SUNY, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1998-1999, Publick Playhouse, Cheverly, MD (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Trojan Women, The Shakespeare Theatre, 1999 March 23-May 08 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1999 Spring, Publick Playhouse, Cheverly, MD (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Grimm Tales, George Mason University Center for the Arts, 1999 March 24-April 11 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1999 July Corcoran Gallery of Art (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Gandhara: East-West Passages, 1999 November 05 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dance Journey: Exploring Dance in Washington, DC, DC Commission on the Arts and Humanities and the Smithsonian Folklife Festival, 2000 June 28 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Int. Ballet Comp., 2000 July 19-30 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Reflections in Motion, 2000 October 07 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 2000-2001 Dance Place (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dana Tai Soon Burgess: Reflections in Motion, presented by the Asian/Pacific American Studies Institute at New York University and the Korean Society, the Kaye Playhouse, Hunter College, 2000 October 07 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Third Benefit for the Eric Hampton/MYB Works Fund, Maryland Youth Ballet & Friends, 2000 October 21 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Dana Tai Soon Burgess & Co. performing Seidenstrasse, Dariush the Supplicant, Mudang, 2000 November 11-12 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Fata Morgana Dance Concert, GDS High School, 2000 December 02 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Mayor's Arts Awards, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - George Mason University Dance Company 2001 Gala Concert, George Mason University, 2001 February 23-24 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Making Waves II, April 7; Making Waves III, April 8, 2001, University of Wisconsin-Madison Asian American Dance Festival, 2001 April 07-08 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 2001 May-September, Arlington's Arts al Fresco (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Metro DC Dance Awards, 2001 June 05 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Joy of Motion Dance Center 25th Anniversary Concert, The Jack Guidone Theater, 2001 September 29-30 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 2001 Fall, Live from National Geographic (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 2001 Fall, Studio Mirror 25th Anniversary Celebration (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Arts & Allies Party, National Gay and Lesbian Task Force Foundation & Dana Tai Soon Burgess and Company, Thursday, November 15, 2001, The Halcyon House, 2001 November 15 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 2001-2002, The Kennedy Center (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Program calendar: Kennedy Center Imagination Celebration Tour, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Trilogy: Helix, Mandala, Silk Roads, 2001 December 07-08 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 2002 May, Asian Pacific American Heritage Month, The Smithsonian Institution (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Dance and The Creative Journey, Opening Event for Asian Pacific American Heritage Month, 2002 May 02 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Five Views - 5 Companies, The George Washington University Department of Theater and Dance, 2002 May 03-04 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Program calendar: Dana Tai Soon Burgess & Company, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Program calendar: Black Rock Center for the Arts, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Program calendar: Lincoln Theatre, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Dana Tai Soon Burgess & Company: A Decade of Dance, 2002 October 05 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - The Nightingale, Kennedy Center, Washington, DC, 2002 December 20-29 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Program calendar: Dance Place, Washington, DC, 2002 December (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Korean American Centennial Celebration, Smithsonian Institution, Washington, DC, 2003 October 30 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Program calendar: Kennedy Center etcetera, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Program calendar: Kennedy Center Modern Dance, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Sharing the Legacy: Dance Masterworks of the 20th Century, 2004 April 02-03 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Tracings, Teatro Municipal, Trujillo, Peru, 2004 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Dana Tai Soon Burgess & Company, Lincoln Theatre, Washington, DC, 2004 November 05 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Dance Works, George Washington University, Washington, DC, 2004 November 18-20 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 20th Annual Mayor's Arts Awards, 2005 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Tracings, Riga, Latvia, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Program calendar: Smithsonian Discovery Theater, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Program calendar: Washington Performing Arts Society, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - john britto's Dance Co., 2007; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Dance Bethesda, 2008; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Ron Paul & Friends, Joy of Motion Dance Center, Washington, DC, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - University of New Mexico, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Eric Hampton Dance, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - East Meets West, Towson State University, Towson, MD, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Urban Journeys: Chinatown, DC, Luna Books, Washington, DC, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Publications, 1988-2010; MS2030 Series 2
  This series contains magazines, newsletters, and other publications, many of which contain articles on Dana Tai Soon Burgess and Moving Forward: Contemporary Asian American Dance Company.
  - A Magazine, 1993-1997 November (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Aamplitude, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Art for the Senses, Publication of the 3rd Annual Asian Heritage Month Festival, May 1-31, 1996, 1996 May 01-31 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Art News, 2000 March (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Artlines, Official Newsletter of the D.C. Commission of the Arts and Humanities, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Arts Washington, Newsletter of the Cultural Alliance of Greater Washington, 2000 October (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Asian American Arts Alliance Dialogue, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Audrey, 2003 October (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Baltimore Magazine, 1995 November-1997 January (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Capital Ventures, Meyer Foundation 1999 Annual Report (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Club Free Time, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Smithsonian Asian Pacific American Program Connections, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Crystal City, Etc., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Cultural Alliance of Greater Washington, 2000 Annual Report (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Dance at the Kennedy Center, Winter 2001 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Dance International, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Dance Magazine, 1994 January-1999 April (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Dance Magazine, 1999 October-2002 April (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Dance View, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Face, 1994 May (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - GW Magazine, 1995-2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - In Step with Moving Forward, The Newsletter for Moving Forward's Dana Tai Soon Burgess & Company, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Kennedy Center News Magazine, 1995 May-2003 December (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - KOAN, Ken Oda's Art Newsletter, 1992 December (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - KoreAm, 2000 November-2003 January (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Korean Culture (fragment), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Korean Society Quarterly, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Korean Update, 1997 June 09 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Mirage, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - The Monthly Magazine of Seoul Arts Center, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Moving Forward: Embracing Our Asian-American Communities Through Contemporary Dance Performance, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Moving Forward: Expression in Contemporary Asian American Dance, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Museletter, Membership newsletter of Washington Performing Arts Society, 1993-2005 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Night & Day, Bimonthly magazine of the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1998 January-February (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Riga Now!, 2005 March (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Rodey View - University of New Mexico, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Second Thoughts, The Woods Academy 2nd Grade newsletter, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Silk Road, A publication of Asians & Friends - Washington, 2000 October-November (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Studio Mirror, 1998 February (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - The Washington Post Magazine, 1994 July 31 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Washingtonian, 1994 April-1998 May (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - "Burgess' theatrical 'Hyphen,'" Washington Times, 2008 October 27; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Dance Place Presents DTSB & Co., 2009 October 09-11; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Dance works Spring '10, 2010 April 15-17; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Danzanueva, 2006 June 11-13; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Washington Post: "New Works Redefine Political Movement", 2009 October 18; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Dept. of state: Dana Tai Soon Burgess, 2009 September; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - "Hyphen", 2010 April 07; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - PDAA, undated; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - The Washington Post: "Retired Burgess Hasn't Lost a Step", 2008 October 27; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - danceviewtimes: "Island, Mainland, Mother Courage', 2009 October 11; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - PDAA Today: "Choreographer- Educator to discuss Value of…", 2010 April 07; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - The Washington Times: "Dance: City Pace is Leaping Forward", 2009 September 11; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - "GW Names Award- Winning artist dana Tai Soon Burgess…", 2009 July 10; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - danceviewtimes: "Journeys", 2009 October 24; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - "Island of Identity", 2009 October 09-11; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Smithsonian Asian Pacific American Program, undated; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Smithsonian Folklife Festival, 2010 July 02; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Asian Pacific American Heritage Month Family Day Celebration, 2009 May 08; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Take Five DTSB & Co. "Exploring the Hyphen", 2009 October 03; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Asian Pacific American Heritage Month- "Dancing Through the..", 2009 May 08; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - The National Chamber Plays Winter concert, 2010 January 19; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - DVD: "DTSB & Co. Island", 2009; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Dance Place "charlie Chan and the Mystery of Love", 2009 October 22-23; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - The Wahington Post: "Omly in america Part Two", 2010 September 12; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Summer Dance Programs at GDS with DTSB & Co., 2010 June 14-July 16; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Times and Places of Norhtwest Washington, 2009 October 14; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - 2010 Smithsonian Folklife Festival Certificate of Appreciation, MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - MSDCmag: "Memories of War Burgess & Co.', 2006 October 19; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - The GW Hatchet: "Spotlight on…", 2009 August 27; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - The Washington Post: "New works Redefine…", 2009 October 18; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Washington: The Entertainers, 2009 November; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Velocity DC Dance Festival, 2010 October 07-09; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Dance Teacher Magazine, 2010 October; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Asian Pacific American Heritage Month Ceremonial, 2010 May 11; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - DTSB&Co Review of Accomplishments, 2009; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Going out Guide Dana Tai Soon Burgess & Company, 2010 October 21; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Service Excellence awards Ceremony, 2010 November 4; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 2010 Service Excellence Celebration Committee, 2010 November; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Charlie Chan and the Mystery of Love flyer, 2010 October 22-24; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Asian Pacific American Heritage Month program, 2010 May 11; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Dancereviewtimes writers on dancing, 2010 October 9; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Washington Post dance} fall arts preview, 2010 September 12; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Washington Post Dance Review, 2010 October 25; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - The Washington Post 2009 Metro D.C. Dance Awards, 2010 September 26; MS2030 Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Publications, 2008-2010; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Administrative files, 1988-2006; MS2030 Series 3
  This series consists of correspondence, contracts, financial records, press releases, and other related publicity material. Miscellaneous materials, such as a dance class flyer and a promotional brochure, are also included in this series.
  - High school identification card belonging to Dana Tai Soon Burgess, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Internet correspondence, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - News releases & interviews, 1997-2004 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Moving Forward Dance Company, Board Member Resource Booklet, 2000 April (Box 5, Folder 8)